We've covered a third of our list,
but so far the Japanese government hasn’t made any response whatsoever.
In any case,
the government refuses to give in...
It was too much to expect of them.
An emergency meeting?
It seems that there are investigators coming
from the U.S. Department of Defense.
We’ve been dispatched here
to investigate the circumstances surrounding the
death of professor Ogura and his bodyguard.
Tosaki-san....
Damn.
Of all things at a time like this.
Well then...
now that we have our secret weapon,
shall we dive right into the second half?
Basic training is over.
Starting today we’re moving onto the real deal.
Sekkinsen kirisaku
Cutting through close combat
♪接近戦　切り裂く♪
Boku no mae ni tatteru omae wa dare da?
Who is the you standing in front of me?
♪僕の前に立っている
お前は誰だ？♪
Nige tsuzukeru mama eien janakute
Running away isn't eternal
♪逃げ続けるのも永遠じゃなくて♪
♪噛み砕き飲み込んだリアルに♪
Kami kudaki nomi konda riaru ni
The reality that I chewed up and swallowed
Shout it out! soshite aimaisa wa
Shout it out! And ambiguity
♪Shout it out
そして曖昧さを断って♪
Datte kage no ayausa wo shirinagara
Was because I knew the danger of the shadow
♪影の危うさを知りながら♪
Aru shu no reisei sugiru shisutemu
A certain system that is too calm
♪ある種の冷静すぎるシステム♪
On On Off ima nara docchi da?
On On Off, what is it right now?
♪ON or OFF 今ならどっちだ？♪
Kekkan me no kanjou wo koroshite
Killing the emotions in the eves and blood
♪結果　何度感情を殺して♪
Aa mureru sousou suginukete
Ah, swarming and missing
♪いいえ　そもそもすり抜けて♪
Kowasarete itta dake
It was only destroyed
♪壊されて　いっただけ♪
♪ほっといてくれ　Craze♪
Hontou itakunaru kureizu
The craze that is truly painful
Boku wa boku de atte seppa tsumattatte
I m who I am, even if I become desperate
♪僕は僕であって
切羽詰まったって♪
Aa iya iya saisho kara risuku dake no sa
Ah, no no, it's filled with risks from the start
♪yeah yeah♪
♪最初からリスクだけのスタート♪
Bukkonde yuke kureizu
Charge in there, craze
♪ぶっこんでいけ　Craze♪
♪むき出す本能　本性で♪
Mukidasu honnou honshou de hatte ikouze
Let's go on with our instincts showing
♪反転攻勢　yeah♪
Kirisaita omae wa dare da?
Who is the you standing in front of me?
♪切り裂いた　お前は誰だ？♪
Kuro-chan, please!
（永井圭(ながいけい)）
ゴム弾… ですか？
Rubber bullets?
（平沢(ひらさわ)）
実地訓練とはいえ
実弾を使うわけにはいかん
I said this would be the real deal,
but we can’t use real weapons.
我々は死んだら終わりだからな
If we died, that’d be the end.
（真鍋(まなべ)）
それでも当たると 相当 いてぇぞ
Even so, those hurt like a bitch
if they hit you.
（圭）
痛みには慣れてますよ
I’m used to pain.
（平沢）
各チームは３人編成
There will be three people per team.
永井はアルファ隊のポイントマンだ
Nagai will be head of the alpha team.
セカンドの私が指揮を執り
テールは真鍋
I’ll be the second,
and Manabe will bring up our rear.
Nakano will...
中野(なかの)は…
ん？
（モニター音声:キャスター）
繰り返しお伝えしています
We repeat.
Earlier,
先ほど 松浪(まつなみ)化学の
田所良一(たどころりょういち)氏と―
Mr. Tadokoro Yoichi and Mr. Kousaku Endou of
Matsunami Sciences were killed.
遠藤耕作(えんどうこうさく)氏が
殺害されました
まだ 他のターゲットを
気にしてるのか
You’re still worried about the other targets?
The suspect, under police surveillance...
Something wrong with that?
（中野攻(なかのこう)）
わりぃかよ
Ajin Satou was seen amidst the panic,
（キャスター）
佐藤の強行に
遭ったとみられ―
and after successive failures by the police, calls have
been made to review security measures.
警察の相次ぐ失態に―
警備態勢の見直しも叫ばれています
Damn.
（攻）
くそっ
（圭のため息）
下手な正義感に
とらわれている余裕はない
We don’t have time to get carried
away by a false sense of justice.
こっちが取れる作戦は…
Do you know our plan?
Tosaki-san is investigating the
Minister’s movements,
トザキさんが大臣の動きを調べて
佐藤(さとう)を待ち伏せする… だろ
and laying an ambush for Satou.
Right?
ふん 覚悟は出来てるようだな
Seems like you’re prepared.
That said,
ていうか 泉(いずみ)さんは？
where’s Izumi-san?
訓練なら同じチームがいいんだけど
I want to be on the same team as
her for training.
戸崎(とさき)さんと研究所だよ
She’s with Tosaki-san at the
Research Facility.
アメリカの役人に
呼び出されたらしい
It seems like they were called
there by the Americans.
（アルメイダ）
では オグラ博士とは…
Then,
you were with Professor Ogura...
（戸崎優(とさきゆう)）
会ったのは
モニタールームだけですね
I only saw him in the monitor room.
永井圭の逃亡を知って
すぐに帰られたので
After Nagai Kei escaped,
I returned home soon after.
After that,
（アルメイダ）
その後 博士は 亜人襲撃の
最中にもかかわらず―
unrelated to the ongoing Ajin attacks,
隔壁の外へ
Professor Ogura was killed by an unknown player outside the barrier wall on the way to his car.
（アルメイダ）
地下の車に戻る途中で
何者かに殺されたと
I don’t know the details,
（戸崎）
私も詳しい状況までは
知りませんが―
but I heard the opposing side was using an IBM.
犯行にはＩＢＭが使われたと
聞きました
（マイヤーズ）
そのように報告は受けています
We’ve received reports of that.
The corpse also matches our medical records.
遺体の歯の治療痕も一致しています
（マイヤーズ）ただ…
（アルメイダ）ただ―
It’s just...
いくつか気になる点がありましてね
There are few points that concern me.
（戸崎）
例えば？
Such as?
（アルメイダ）
例えば―
Such as,
なぜ 殺害時の監視カメラ映像が
消えているのか
why is the surveillance camera video missing
on the site of the murder?
確かに妙ですが―
That is mysterious,
but that might be the result of Satou’s explosion.
佐藤の起こした爆発の衝撃が
原因かもしれません
（アルメイダ）
博士とボディーガードの遺体が―
It’s also unnatural that the bodies of Professor Ogura
別の場所で発見されているのも
不自然です
and his bodyguard were found at different locations.
Perhaps they got separated while escaping?
逃げる途中で
バラバラになっただけでは？
We’ve also heard that on the day of the event,
当日―
施設にいたはずの研究員が―
one of the research staff who was supposed
to be at the facility went missing.
行方不明になっているとの
話もあります
That’s the first time I’ve heard of that.
それは初耳ですね
Are you sure that’s been confirmed
against the staff list?
職員リストじゃ そんな事実は
確認されていないはずですが
あなたは オグラ博士が
モニタールームを出た後―
You see.
So, after Professor Ogura left
the monitor room,
you went outside the barrier wall,
am I correct?
隔壁の外へ出ていますね？
フッ
No way!
まさか 私を疑ってるんですか？
Are you seriously considering
me as a suspect?
もし仮に―
Let’s say, that the crime wasn’t
an act of Satou,
佐藤ではなく
内部の者の犯行だとすると―
but rather someone on the inside.
The only one who could have murdered the professor given the conditions is you.
状況的に博士を殺害出来るのは―
Tosaki San!
戸崎さん あなただけなんです
It could only be you.
なぜ 私がそんな事をする必要が
あるんです？
Why do you think I would need to
do such a thing?
（アルメイダ）
私に分かるのは―
All I know is that,
亜人襲撃の
真っ最中にもかかわらず―
despite the ongoing Ajin attacks,
you were outside the facility for close to an hour.
あなたが１時間近くも
外に出ていたということだけです
なぜ そんな危険なまねを？
Why would you do such a dangerous thing?
（戸崎）
実は…
The truth is,
永井の逃亡を知った上司に
電話でひどく責められましてね
After Nagai’s escape, my boss called me
and really got on my case about it.
I was unable to control myself,
and had to leave.
居ても立っても
いられなかったんです
役人のつらさは
あなた方もご存じでしょう？
I’m sure
you too know the difficulty of being
a public official.
ふんっ
The proof of the circumstances is
extremely limited.
（マイヤーズ）
状況証拠は極めて乏しいです
I guess,
やはり あの男は
博士殺害とは関係ないのでは？
he really isn’t connected with the
professor’s murder.
君の意見は聞いてない
I didn’t ask for your opinion.
す… すいません
I’m sorry.
（アルメイダ）
フッ
時間の無駄だったな
That was a waste of time.
遺留品を回収して帰国する
申請を出しておけ
Gather the evidence and we’ll return home.
Put in the request.
（ため息）
（テレビ音声:キャスター）
速報です
News Flash
After noon today,
本日 昼過ぎ―
there was an explosion at the headquarters
of Touyou Railroad Industries.
東陽(とうよう)レイロード産業
本社ビルにて―
爆破事件が起きました
この事件で 同社
会長の湯谷(ゆたに)氏と―
In the explosion, Director Yutani,
他３人の死亡が
確認されています
as well as three other victims,
were confirmed dead.
Ritori Makoto                         Toyou Railroad              James Campbell
（マーカーの音）
The four victims
（キャスター）
死亡した４名は いずれも―
were all targets on Satou’s list,
亜人 佐藤による
殺害リストの対象者であり―
In response to the government's stance,
強硬姿勢を示した政府に対する―
people are calling for the capture of Satou
佐藤の応酬ではとの声も
挙がっています
連続する
佐藤の凶行に―
Among continuing panic caused by Satou,
demonstrations are being held near government offices.
官庁周辺では
デモ行為が続いています
Hey, did you see the news about Ajin?
（看護師１）
ねぇ 亜人のニュース見た？
Yeah. It’s scary, isn’t it.
（看護師２）
ええ 怖いわよね
That girl in the hospital,
（看護師１）
例の病室の子
she’s Nagai Kei’s sister, isn’t she?
（看護師１）お兄さんが永井圭なのよ
（看護師２）それ―
Yeah, that’s the Ajin who was on
the news before, right?
この前 話題になった亜人でしょ？
屋上から 人 突き落として
施設から逃げたっていう
The one who pushed someone from the roof
of a building, and ran away from the facility.
（看護師１）
心配よねぇ
I’m worried...
It’s become a difficult world for
Ajin to live in.
（オグラ･イクヤ）
亜人も生きづらい世の中に
なったなぁ
愛煙家と同じだ
Just like for heavy smokers.
（圭）
佐藤さんを止めれば
以前の日常に戻りますよ
If we stop Satou,
the day-to-day will return to normal.
Unlike cigarettes,
亜人は たばこと違って
他人に害はない
Ajin don’t harm others.
だといいがな
One can hope.
A secret weapon, huh.
（奥山(おくやま)）
秘密兵器か…
こういうの
作ってみたかったんだよなぁ
I always wanted to try making something like this.
We refuse to give in to terrorism.
（モニター音声:総理大臣）
我々はテロに屈することなく―
国民の安全を脅かす
亜人の組織を壊滅するため―
In order to destroy the Ajin organization that
is threatening our populace,
I plan to put new laws in place.
新たな法整備を取るしだいです
This has gotten pretty intense.
（高橋(たかはし)）
なんか すげぇことになってきたな
At this rate, things for Ajin are just getting worse.
（ゲン）
これじゃ 亜人の立場は
悪くなるばっかりだよ
Are you unhappy?
（田中功次(たなかこうじ)）
不満なのか？
まさか
No way.
Are we really handling things the right way?
でも 今のやり方で
大丈夫なのかなぁ
だったら 他にどんな方法がある
What other choice do we have?
That is...
それは…
確かに 亜人への風当たりは
強くなった
It’s true
that outward criticism of Ajin has gotten stronger.
But I wouldn’t say it’s all bad.
でも 悪い事ばっかじゃねぇだろ
We’ve gathered Ajin from all over Japan.
（田中）
ここには今
日本中の亜人が集まってきてる
前に厚労省に来たやつらや―
Guys from the ‘protest’ at the Ministry,
and groups we got through your connections.
お前らの つてを
頼ってきたグループもいる
The police can’t prevent information from travelling by word of mouth.
警察も口コミは
防ぎようがねぇからな
みんな―
亜人の未来のために
立ち上がったんだ
Everyone has come together for the future of all Ajin.
It’s too late to turn back.
今さら後には引けねぇよ
（木村(きむら)）
田中さん
Tanaka-san.
（木村）
とりあえず みんなには
爆弾作りを手伝ってもらってますが
Right now I’m getting everyone
to help with assembling the bomb, but...
（田中）
ああ わりぃな
Ah. Thank you.
Is there anything else that needs to be done?
他に 今 何かやる事は？
Hmm, clean-up, I guess.
うーん… 掃除とか？
分かりました
Understood.
I’m acting as the manager,
私がまとめ役ですので
何かあれば教えてください
so if anything comes up, please let me know.
ハッ ちょっとした軍隊並みだな
Ha, this is starting to feel like an army.
ていうか あいつ何て名前だっけ？
That is...
What was his name again?
フフッ さすがは田中さんだ
That’s just like you, Tanaka-san.
はぁ？　どういう意味だよ？
Huh? What’s that supposed to mean?
（高橋）
それより 肝心の佐藤さんは？
More importantly, where’s our main man Satou-san?
ああ…
ちょっと前から 姿が見えないけど
Ah, I haven’t seen him for a while.
Isn’t that obvious?
そりゃあ 決まってんだろ
（戸崎）
ああ 分かった
Yes.
Understood.
名阪医療センターの
柏木(かしわぎ)氏が殺された
Mr. Kashiwagi of the Meihan Medical Center has been killed.
It seems the incident happened while
he was traveling by bullet train.
走行中の新幹線で
犯行にあったようだ
（マーカーの音）
It’s our turn, Tosaki-san.
出番ですよ 戸崎さん
The Minister who’s the next target is..
（戸崎）
次のターゲットとなる大臣は今―
合同庁舎の危機管理室に
こもっている
currently holed up in the safe room
at the government building.
However, given the way the attacks on the
related companies were carried out,
だが 関連企業が
相次いで被害に遭い―
I believe we ought to take additional measures.
新たな法案も可決される
The Minister is also being pressed to deal
with related government authorities,
大臣も関係省庁の対応に追われ―
and the Cabinet is trying to
get their story straight.
内閣次官と会って
口裏を合わせるようだ
すでに密談の場所は割り出した
I’ve already inferred where they’ll
hold their private meeting.
It’s a place that important people
from many countries often use.
各国の要人が使う施設だ
I thought you said the attack would come at
the ministry, or at home, or both.
襲撃されるのは 厚労省か自宅
もしくは料亭だったはずでは？
あくまでも予想と言ったはずだ
それに―
I said that was a prediction at best.
And what’s more,
永井 お前なら
多少の変更にも対応出来るだろう
Nagai.
You of all people should be able to deal
with some changes here and there.
あ…
まあ 作戦は絶えず応用するのが
基本ですからね
Well...
the point of the strategy was to make
use of the building layout.
フンッ
Hirasawa, get a copy of the architectural blueprints,
平沢は建築図面を手に入れ
人員配置を検討しろ
and investigate where people will
be posted around the building.
Roger.
（平沢）
はい
I will get my hands on a detailed schedule.
（戸崎）
私は詳細なスケジュールを
手に入れる
残りの者は訓練の精度を上げろ
Everyone else, notch up your training.
Alright!
（攻）
よーしっ！
行くぞ 下村(しもむら)君
Let’s go,
Shimomura-kun.
戸崎さん
Tosaki-san.
ここから先は １分１秒を争います
From here on,
we’ll be fighting every second of the way.
失敗は許されませんよ
We can’t afford any mistakes.
フッ 誰に向かって言っている？
Who do you think you’re talking to?
（戸崎）
失礼します
Excuse me.
（大臣）
佐藤を捕獲出来ないばかりか―
No matter what you try,
you can’t capture Satou, huh.
スポンサーは壊滅
Our sponsors have been annhihilated.
失態続きの貴様が
よく顔を出せたな
How dare you show your face here after
such continued mismanagement.
My apologies.
（戸崎）
申し訳ありません
However,
しかし 大臣に
もしもの事がないようにと…
Minister, I came to prevent the same
kind of accident from happening to-
（大臣）
ここは核シェルターみたいなものだ
This place is like any other shelter.
（大臣）
いくら亜人だろうと 手は出せん
They may be Ajin,
but they won’t be able to get in.
That said,
（戸崎）
とはいえ 外出されることがあれば
話は別です
if you were to take a trip outside, that’s a different story.
念のためにスケジュールを…
If I could get your schedule just to be sure-
笑わせるな
Don’t make me laugh.
Like I would discuss the situation with to
a subordinate who’s about to be fired.
すぐに除名する無能な部下に―
何を相談しろと？
う…
（大臣）
それに 他人の心配をする暇など
あるまい
And besides,
you shouldn’t have the time to be
worrying about others.
曽我部(そかべ)によれば―
According to Sokabe,
aren’t you under investigation by the Americans?
国防総省の連中が いろいろと
探っているそうじゃないか
既に聴取も終わりましたし―
They’ve already finished their interrogation.
They have no reason to doubt me.
私に疑われるような事は
何もありませんよ
Through the police crime lab, we got
hold of Professor Ogura’s effects,
（曽我部(そかべ)）
オグラ博士の遺留品は
警察の鑑識を経て―
こちらに移管されました
and have transferred control of them here.
（曽我部）
移管時の照合リストは
先にお渡ししたとおりです
The list of items is as I gave to you earlier.
（マイヤーズ）
確認に時間を下さい
Please allow us some time to confirm.
（アルメイダ）
ん？
問題ありません
遺留品は全てそろって…
I see no problems.
相変らず 観察力はゼロだな
Your detection skills are as low as ever.
はっ…
As I thought.
やはりな
Something that should be here is missing.
ここにあるはずの物が
なぜか無くなっている
What should we do?
（下村泉(しもむらいずみ)）
どうするんですか
How are we supposed to get the schedule at this rate?
この状況で
どうやってスケジュールを…
心配はいらん
Don’t worry.
If we can’t get it directly from the Minister,
大臣から聞き出せないなら
近い人間を狙うまでだ
we’ll go after someone close to him.
I sent the schedule over earlier.
（秘書）
スケジュールは先ほど送信しました
はい まだ亜人研究所です
Yes.
I’m still at the Ajin Research Facility.
資料を集め終わりしだい…
As soon as I assemble the documents-
（戸崎）
大臣秘書が今
新法案の資料を精査中だ
The Minister’s secretary is examining
the documents for a new bill.
I’m also supposed to submit a report.
私も報告書を出すことになっている
その隙にスケジュールを奪う
That’s our chance to steal the schedule.
あ…
（泉）これは…？
（戸崎）メモリーの認識と―
This is...?
It will take about 10 seconds between recognizing
the device and automatically
データ移動の自動実行に約10秒
executing the program.
Don’t let her catch you during
those ten seconds.
その間だけ気付かれるな
You mean...
それって…
ＩＢＭが出せる 君の仕事だ
Your job is to control the IBM.
Sorry, can’t you wait?
（秘書）
悪いけど後にしてくれない？
I’m sorry,
すいません 戸崎さんが
急ぎで確認してほしいと…
Tosaki-san asked me to hurry and confirm...
はぁ… 亜人のせいで
馬鹿みたいな仕事ばっかり
It’s the Ajins’ fault I have to do
all this idiotic work.
ちっ データでよこしなさいよ…
You ought to send it digitally.
（泉）
クロちゃん お願い
Kuro-chan,
please!
（秘書）
ま いいんじゃない？
大臣に渡しとくわ
Looks okay to me.
I’ll pass it on to the minister.
あ あの…
...that... that is...
何？
What?
いや その…
That’s, uh...
That’s...
（泉）
そ その時計 すてきですね
よく似合ってます
a very nice watch.
It looks good on you.
あー 分かっちゃった？
Oh, you noticed?
The truth is, it’s an antique-one of a kind!
実はこれ
アンティークの 一点ものなの
ウッ フフフ
（ため息）
（秘書）
このスーツもミニマムだけど
一応はハイブランドだし―
This suit is simplistic, but it’s high-brand.
ヒールもオートクチュールで
結構 高かったのよ
And the heels are haute-couture,
so they were pretty expensive.
That’s very impressive.
す すごいですね…
（秘書）
よかったら ショップ教えるけど？
If you’d like,
I’ll tell you where I got them from?
あ ありがとうございます
また 機会があれば…
Thank you very much.
Maybe another time.
（秘書）
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute.
え？
あなた―
You...
are you and Tosaki-san an item?
戸崎さんとデキてる？
は？
Ha?
（秘書）
いっつも一緒にいるし―
You’re always together,
彼の命令なら何でも聞くんでしょ？
and you do whatever he commands,
isn’t that right?
I’m just doing my job.
（泉）私は ただ 自分の仕事を…
（秘書）はっきり言って―
Just say it!
趣味悪いよ？
No sense in hiding things.
Our basic strategy is to shoot from behind
the IBM, which we’ll use as a shield.
（圭）
基本は幽霊を盾に後方射撃
（攻）
うぉおおお おおおっ！
（圭）
作戦は佐藤さんの確保が最優先
The primary objective is to secure Satou-san.
見つけしだい 無力化を狙う！
To render him powerless the moment
we find him.
（圭ＩＢＭ）
馬鹿が！
Idiot!
Don’t underestimate my training!
俺の運動神経なめんな！
わざとだよ
I meant to do this!
（銃の音）
ん… なんで俺が…
Why do I have to be.... Satou...
佐藤なんだ…
That’s a new record.
（平沢）
記録更新だ
（圭）
あとは 戸崎さんの連絡を
待つだけです
Now
all we have to do is wait for word
from Tosaki-san.
（泉）
え… これって 今夜…
This means... tonight??
くそ 下村は何をやってる
Damn.
What the hell is Shimomura doing?
（窓をたたく音）
What is it?
（戸崎）
何の用です？
もう聴取は終わったはずですが
The investigation should be over.
（アルメイダ）
実は 最後に 一つ
気になることがありまして
Actually, we found something in
the end that concerned us.
オグラ博士の遺留品に―
Something seems to be missing from
among Professor Ogura’s effects.
あるはずの物が
なぜか見当たらないんです
（戸崎）
遺留品？
His effects?
恐らく 誰かが保管庫から
回収したんでしょう
We suspect
it was picked up while they were in storage.
オグラ博士の車に
残されていたはずの―
They were supposed to be left in Professor
Ogura’s car, these...cigarettes.
これをね
あ…
Oh?
おや 心当たりが？
Look familiar?
何のことか知らないが―
I don’t know what you’re talking about,
尋問なら正式な手続きを
取ってもらいたいな
but if you want a cross-examination, you’ll have
to go through the appropriate procedures.
（アルメイダ）
ふん…
確かに おっしゃるとおりですね
It’s exactly... as you say.
（戸崎）
では 私も忙しいので これで…
Well then, I’m in a hurry, so...
（注射器を刺す音）
なっ…
（アルメイダ）
いいかげん
日本式の面倒な手続きには飽きた
I’m tired of dealing with Japan’s procedures.
さっさと口を割らせてもらうよ
I’ll make you talk.
車を回せ
Bring around the car.
Should we really be doing this?
ほ 本当にいいんですか？
日本の公務員に こんなまねを
To a Japanese official.
Didn’t I say I don't need your opinion?
君の意見は聞いてないと
言ったはずだが？
If it comes down to it,
we’ll say he was in an accident.
（アルメイダ）
いざとなれば
事故に遭ってもらうまでだ
ここは
人の死に鈍感な連中ばかりだしな
Everyone around here is so insensitive to death.
なっ！
（泉）
ああっ！
あの女 いつも一緒にいた…
That woman...
she’s always been with him.
仕方ない 拘束しろ
We have no choice.
Contain her too.
Out of my way!
邪魔っ！
（亜人を止められる音）
え…！？
（泉）ま まさか…
（マイヤーズ）この女！
No way, this woman...!
この女 亜人です！
This woman is an Ajin!
（泉）
さっき出したばかりだから…
Because I just brought one out...
ぐっ… ああっ…
（マイヤーズ）
内臓を破壊したから
持って数分ってところね
Your internal organs are destroyed.
It should take a few minutes.
If the Ajin’s consciousness is lost...
本体と意識の伝達が途絶えれば―
ＩＢＭなんか ただの人形
the IBM is just a doll.
趣味の悪いオブジェにもならない
It’s not even good as a curio.
（アルメイダ）
あの男も
隠れて亜人を飼ってたわけか
So that man was keeping an Ajin too...
いい実験材料が増えたな
That’s good, more subjects for
our experiments.
（マイヤーズ）
残念ね
普通に死ねたら幸せだったのに
That’s too bad.
You’d have been happier dead.
（カーステレオの音）
（舌打ち）
（マイヤーズ）
あっ…
あっ！
よせ！　目撃されたら面倒だ！
Leave it.
We can’t afford any witnesses.
（平手打ちの音）
（マイヤーズ）うっ…
（アルメイダ）
こいつを締め上げるほうが先だ
Tying him up is our first priority.
Get the car moving!
さっさと車を出せ
（アルメイダ）
心配するな　あの女の分は…
Don’t worry.
Afterwards I’ll use you to make up for what
we lost out on with that woman.
あとでお前に使ってやる
ミスの責任は
きっちり取らないとな
Gotta take responsibility for your mistakes.
（戸崎）
君の仕事は何だ？
What is your job?
My job is...
（泉）
私の仕事は…
to protect you!
あなたを守ることです
To be Continued...
Mou akitakara koukan shiyou
Since I'm tired of it, let's exchange it
♪もう飽きたから交換しよう♪
Omae ga motteru futsuu no to
With the normal one that you are holding
♪お前が持ってる普通のと♪
Kira kira shiteru kami no kaado to
A shining paper card and
♪キラキラしてる神のカードと♪
Zara zara shiteru kami no kaado
A rough paper card
♪ザラザラしてる紙のカード♪
Kondo uchi ni kitara
Next time you come to my house
♪今度家に来たら♪
Zenbu miseteyaru yo dakara
I'll show you everything, so...
♪全部見せてやるよ♪
♪だから♪
Koutei no sumi ni futari, kaze ga fuite ima
At the edge of the schoolyard the wind blows...
♪校庭の隅に二人 風が吹いて♪
♪今なら言えるかな♪
nara ieru ka na?
can I say it now?
Dare nimo iwanai kotoba
Words never spoken to another person
♪誰にも言わない言葉♪
Yasashiku suru kara asobi ni kite yo
I'll be gentle so come and play often
♪「優しくするから
遊びに来てよ」♪
Nandemo ageru yo, ne
I'll give you anything, hey
♪「何でもあげるよ ねぇ」♪
Korekara zutto tomodachi de ite yo
Let's be friends forever
♪「これからずっと
友達でいてよ」♪
Preview
It’s tough
being a dog.